[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[OVERDO]
[Episode 24]
Triumph for our heroes,
safe return for all!
Triumph for our heroes...
On the battlefield,
weapons are blind
and perils abound.
Are you really willing to
leave your family
and business behind?
Family?
What family?
But as for you, Ms. Ye,
have you really given up
on studying abroad?
It's my honor to defend my country.
Besides,
if Qingyu were still here,
he'd have made the same choice.
Triumph for our heroes,
safe return for all!
Stop!
[Answering the call to arms
to defend our homeland]
He can finally let go of the past
and start a new life.
Isn't this exactly what I want to see?
He hates me so much now.
Telling him about this
would just be asking for humiliation.
Even if the road ahead is tough,
I will raise our child well on my own.
Miss Ren,
where are you going?
Inspector Li, you think too highly of me.
In my current state,
where else can I go?
Then get in
and return
to the hospital with me.
We walk different paths.
Why are you in my business?
Then should I
just let you murder my father?
You're a filial son, huh?
But if you shield a criminal,
you can kiss your
police badge goodbye.
I will get to the bottom
of the North-South Railway case.
But before that,
I'll never let you hurt the innocent.
The innocent?
Who's innocent?
Li Rongzhang?
You investigating
and I seeking revenge are
both just ways to validate our own paths.
May the best man win.
The batch of arms
on the Fang family's ship
did belong to my father's army.
Are you admitting that
Li Rongzhang killed my father?
On the contrary.
The transactions between
my father and Master Fang had been
going on for 5 years.
They always used the guise
of transporting military medical supplies
to transport arms and gunpowder.
And about this matter,
Master Fang was well aware.
So it's completely untrue
that my father smuggled arms
and caused the ship to explode.
Are you trying to say
that the explosion
was an accident?
[Marine Logbook of the Remote Star]
The ship Master Fang was on,
the Remote Star,
made countless round trips
between Nancheng and Nanyang.
Every time it left the port,
there were safety officers
to make a record.
You can check out
the previous draft levels.
[Ship Logbook]
Only the draft of the last departure was
deeper than before.
You mean the ship
carried things other than arms,
[Ship Logbook]
but there's no record of it?
So what exactly
was added to the ship,
and who did it belong to?
How is it
related to Master Fang
leaving your wedding
to rush back to Nanyang?
And what role did it play
in that explosion?
Aren't you curious?
What are you getting at?
Ren Susu,
face reality.
The Fangs have fallen,
and the Murongs won't acknowledge you.
As a mere orphan,
be it to seek revenge
or investigate the matter,
you have to risk your life.
But can you afford to risk your life now?
Don't you care
about your child?
Qingyi is my family,
so I will take good care of his child.
And my father is
even more so my family.
So I will clear his name.
Why do you need to prove
to a nobody like me
that the Lis are innocent?
Aren't you afraid that the end result...
If it really has to do with my father,
then regardless of
new grudges or old debts,
I swear by the police badge on my cap
that I'll bring
the real culprit to justice
and get justice for the innocent dead.
Stop the car.
See her out.
Qingyu,
don't worry.
I'll protect everyone
in both of our families.
Everything here...
will remain the same.
♪ The more passionate ♪
♪ Our past embrace ♪
Those days 3 years ago
♪ The more icy ♪
were actually very short.
♪ Our present clash ♪
Qingyi,
you should hate me.
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
If one day
I can no longer love you,
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
the only thing that'll keep me alive
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
is my hatred for you.
So,
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
I'd rather time freeze at this second.
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
♪ Bind you and me ♪
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
♪ Together, we fall ♪
We won! We won!
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
We won! We won!
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
Principal,
we won!
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
We won! We won!
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
We won! We won!
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Must be together ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Le'an.
It's snowing!
Where are you running to?
Mom, it's snowing.
It's too cold.
Come on,
I'll take you back inside.
I want to play in the snow.
[Upholding his elder brother's unfulfilled
legacy and heeding the nation's call,]
[Murong Qingyi led aviation students to the
southwestern front, to serve the country.]
[Through the arduous, perilous journey,
he achieved great feats with patriotic zeal.]
[The fires of war raged for 6 long years;
6 years since he left his homeland.]
[Congratulations on the full opening
of the North-South Railway]
[Nancheng Station]
Bravo! Bravo!
Marshal Li,
the North-South Railway
is officially open.
As the person in charge,
care to say a few words?
After a turbulent few decades,
the North-South Railway
is finally fully operational.
I shoulder a heavy responsibility.
I promise to use this railway
to benefit the people.
Bravo! Bravo!
Mr. Zhang!
The Zhang family has invested heavily
in this railway construction.
Regarding this,
what are your future business plans?
[Nancheng Station]
It's an honor for the Zhangs
to cooperate with Marshal Li.
In the future,
this railway will
also be the main transport artery
for our pharmaceutical factory.
We'll supply
high-quality, low-cost medicines
to the public and the military.
Bravo! Bravo!
-Bravo!
-Great!
Bravo!
Gentlemen, please look over here.
Marshal Li.
Foreigner's dog piss...
No thanks.
The landscape of Nancheng
has changed drastically in 7 years.
Now that the Murongs are weakened,
you've become the real shot-caller.
Our Zhang family also
feels deeply honored.
Are you dropping hints at me?
No.
Yes,
your family
has contributed money and effort.
But you must get one thing straight:
With or without your family,
I'm still the one calling the shots
about the North-South Railway.
Naturally.
I have no intention of claiming credit.
I'm just here to propose a deal
on behalf of my father.
As long as
you open the door of convenience
for us on the railway,
the medicines we produce will be
supplied to the military first.
And of all pharmaceutical sales...
you'll get a 10% cut.
[Lanxin Theater]
Susu,
you're here.
What did you find out?
On this trip back to Nanyang,
I finally found the Fangs' old butler,
Mr. Bao.
When Uncle Fang's ship sank,
he was supposed to be on it.
He told me...
These are all arms.
Lash them down for the rough seas.
Look at this!
Lash it down tight.
The German arms bought by Li Rongzhang
over the years
were basically transported by the Fangs
via sea routes to Nancheng.
Nothing ever went wrong with this before.
But that one time,
a sailor found something
that had never been there before
under the arms.
Some sailors
secretly took those pills
and started behaving abnormally,
while others became lethargic.
What are you two doing?
What's wrong with you?
How dare you smoke opium?
If Master finds out, you'll all be fired!
Mr. Bao,
th-this isn't opium.
I-It's medicine.
Medicine?
According to the sailors,
this medicine is
extremely popular in Nanyang,
as it boosts your energy.
So, Mr. Bao let his guard down.
He didn't want to offend the Lis
over his sailors stealing the medicine,
so he suppressed the matter.
But, a few days later,
the sailors who took the medicine
started getting sick—
high fevers and rashes
that even seemed contagious.
Come!
So, Mr. Bao sent a telegram
to Uncle Fang to handle it quickly.
Uncle Fang replied and warned him
not to let anyone
leave the ship and go ashore,
lest there be an accident.
Mr. Bao was both afraid of
catching the strange disease
and of being punished by Uncle Fang,
so he secretly went ashore
in a small boat.
As a result,
he escaped the explosion.
What were the pills
on the ship called?
The sailors called them
Red Pills.
Red Pills?
Isn't that a drug?
They weren't ordinary Red Pills.
With Mr. Bao as a witness
and the Red Pills as evidence,
we can kill
that old bastard Li!
Li Rongzhang can't die yet.
Why?
If Li Rongzhang is
really a link in this drug chain,
killing him
will cut off our trail.
To eradicate the Red Pills,
we must follow the trail
and find the source.
I only heard of Red Pills
appearing in coastal areas,
but they actually spread to Nancheng.
This is no small matter.
No matter how serious,
it's for the authorities to handle.
The Red Pill
not only physically
destroys the addicts,
but also has absolute control
over their minds.
If we let it spread,
sooner or later,
there will be no more usable soldiers.
So,
you don't want revenge anymore?
Of course I want revenge.
-How long?
-Just…
A year, 2 years, or 10 years?
Every day the Red Pill matter
remains unsolved
is a day Li Rongzhang retains power!
How's that justified?
In today's
dog-eat-dog world,
truth and justice are but myths!
Don't forget what
we've been planning for all these years.
Ren Susu,
you can wait,
but I can't.
All these years,
my brother has appeared
in my dreams every night,
charred all over,
covered in blood,
crying out for me to avenge him.
Qing!
I won't persuade you,
so don't you try to persuade me.
I'll avenge
my brother and Mr. Fang
myself.
[Xanadu Cabaret]
Your hairpin.
Thank you, sir.
Who sent you?
No one.
Li Rongzhang, you have
so much blood on your hands.
I'm your retribution!
Retribution?
I'd like to see
if I'm afraid of retribution
or if retribution's afraid of me.
This retribution is quite a beauty.
Get lost.
Marshal,
we should take her back for interrogation.
Many people want me dead.
I have no interest in knowing why.
Li Rongzhang!
If you don't kill me today,
you'll regret it!
You should be glad
that I like the look of you today.
Want to kill me?
Oh, kid...
Why are you here?
What's with that look?
Are you afraid of me?
Or do you hate me?
What happened to your hand?
I tried to kill Li Rongzhang and got hurt.
It's a pity.
That old bastard sure is lucky.
I couldn't make him die on the streets.
I knew it.
You and Ren Susu are working together.
So you knew all along
that she'd try to assassinate my father
at Qingyu's wedding.
So what if I knew?
Doesn't he deserve to die?
What about me?
What am I to you,
exactly?
Just a casual fling,
or a premeditated scheme?
Or has there ever been
a part of you
that loved me even a tiny bit?
You are Li Rongzhang's son.
What do you think?
I understand.
So from the very beginning,
to you,
I've always been an enemy.
As long as my surname's Li,
you'll never trust me.
You've never truly
shed your mask for me either.
It was all my wishful thinking.
I was delusional.
Li Boze!
Can you give up your status
as the young master of the Lis?
Can you?
If you can...
You can try to kill him as many times
as you want...
but I won't let you
lay a finger on my father!
Look!
-There's a plane!
-A plane?
It's a plane!
-It's a plane from the aviation school!
-Really?
Really?
We won at the frontlines! They're back!
They're here!
Young Marshal Murong,
it's been 7 years.
How does it feel to be back?
You triumphed in battle.
Care to share your experience?
The North-South Railway is
now owned by the Lis,
and the Murongs are weakened.
-Which side are you on?
-As Zhenhua Aviation School's principal,
how do you feel right now?
Please say something.
The Murongs have produced
two aviation school principals.
Do you have anything to say?
Young Master Qingyi,
why are you back a few days early?
The higher-ups told me to return early
to probe military corruption.
Oh, right.
Take a look at this.
Seen it before?
This is...
This is a new type of drug
we found in the military.
Principal,
this was found in the military camp.
It's probably made from opium.
It has spread its way to Nancheng.
My informant told me that
Li Rongzhang is suspected of
funding his army through corruption.
Would Marshal Li do that?
Who cares if he would or not.
I came back this time
to resolve this case.
Otherwise,
this drug will cause endless harm.
Upon learning of your return,
both the Murongs and the Lis
sent word immediately.
The Murongs want you home for dinner,
while Marshal Li has
set up a banquet at Lanxin Theater
to welcome you.
Where should we go first?
For the Red Pill investigation,
I can't miss
the Lis' dinner.
Let's go.
[Lanxin Theater]
Qiaoqiao,
where are you?
Where'd this low-life come from?
Trying to get killed?
Apologize.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Get lost.
Thank you, Mister.
It's dangerous to be on the street alone.
I...
Qiaoqiao ran onto the street.
I came out to find it.
Don't do such a dangerous thing again,
you hear me?
If Qiaoqiao's in danger again,
I will save it again.
Qiaoqiao is my family.
Yes,
a real man should
protect his family well.
Mister.
Where's your family?
My family...
went to a faraway place.
My dad went to a faraway place too.
Where's your home?
I'll take you back.
Lanxin Theater.
My mom and I live there.
Let's go.
Come on.
[Lanxin Theater]
After you.
To the left.
I heard that
the boss of Lanxin Theater
has a rich patron backing her.
More than that;
she even had a child for that patron.
No wonder.
There's no way she could've
just opened such a big theater.
-So it's shady business.
-Mister, let's go.
Le'an,
if you hear nonsense in the future,
just cover your ears.
Don't listen to it, okay?
But if I cover my ears,
will they stop talking nonsense?
I still have to face it myself.
Mister,
be more mature, okay?
You're so sensible.
Mister,
let's go.
Where could he've gone?
Have you searched everywhere?
We've searched every corner
of the theater.
Could Young Master Le'an have run outside?
I'll go outside to look.
Boss,
we've found Young Master Le'an.
He was brought back by a kind stranger.
That's great.
Reward him properly
with more money.
But the gentleman said
he must deliver the child
to his mother in person.
Where is he?
He's on his way up.
Boss,
this gentleman
brought Young Master Le'an back.
Mom!
You scared me to death.
Sir, the dog.
Yes.
Yan,
take Le'an to play.
Sir...
thank you for bringing Le'an back.
Sorry for the trouble.
No trouble at all.
Le'an is
quite cute.
I'm really sorry.
It's...
It's not convenient for me to go out,
so I couldn't thank you in person.
You manage such a large business
with all sorts of people.
It's better to be more careful.
You're right.
The theater is hectic.
I should take better care of Le'an.
Since the child's been found,
I'll take my leave.
Goodbye.
Madam,
is the perfume balm
you're wearing
Fruhjahr?
♪ In those fleeting
three seconds of twilight ♪
Yes.
♪ An amber dream shimmers
within the glass ♪
What about it?
♪ The ice of loneliness
melts away in the warmth ♪
Nothing.
♪ Your evasive gaze
gives your heart away ♪
It just reminds me of an old friend.
She loved to use this brand too.
♪ Don't tell me ♪
It seems...
♪ You're tired again; this time, don't ♪
you miss this friend very much.
♪ Don't push me away
only to draw me close ♪
Miss her?
♪ Why so nervous? ♪
♪ Please don't stay frozen for too long ♪
♪ Say my name ♪
I'd rather
♪ Please don't stop ♪
I had never met her.
♪ Forgive me, I've loved you for ages ♪
♪ Please lull me into absolute surrender ♪
♪ Before you cage me
in a prison of your design ♪
♪ Stop bowing to the crowd ♪
♪ Conquer to be free ♪
♪ Even if I'm unrepentantly obsessed ♪
Right.
♪ I'll let the wrongs just carry on ♪
Missing out on certain people
♪ Drunk and unawakened,
waves rage stronger ♪
may be a blessing in disguise.
♪ Let them rage, let them rise ♪
♪ Drench me through ♪
♪ Come with me if you're brave ♪
I'm sorry.
I've
overshared.
Goodbye.
♪ Again and again, knowing the danger ♪
♪ Again and again, testing the limits ♪
♪ Forgive me, I've loved you for ages ♪
♪ Please lull me into absolute surrender ♪
♪ Before you cage me
in a prison of your design ♪